sbm.gov.in 2017-06-11

# Website Policies | Ministry of Drinking Water and Sanitation, GOI

## Privacy Policy

As a general rule, this website does not collect Personal Information about you when you visit the site. You can generally visit the site without revealing Personal Information, unless you yourself choose to provide such information  
This website records your visits and logs the following information for statistical purposes -your server"s address; the name of the top-level domain from which you access the Internet (for example, .gov, .com, .in, etc.); the type of browser you use; the date and time you access the site; the pages you have accessed; and the documents downloaded and the previous Internet address from which you linked directly to the site. We will not identify users or their browsing activities, except when a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the service provider"s logs.  
Your email address will only be recorded if you choose to send a message. It will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it and will not be added to a mailing list. Your email address will not be used for any other purpose, and will not be disclosed, without your consent.  
If you are asked for any other Personal Information you will be informed how it will be used. If at any time you believe the principles referred to in this privacy statement have not been followed, or have any other comments on these principles, please notify the concerned through the contact us page.  
The use of the term "Personal Information" in this privacy statement refers to any information from which your identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained

* * *

## Hyperlink Policies

Links to external websites/portals  
At many places in this website, you shall find links to other websites/portals. This links have been placed for your convenience. This Ministry is not responsible for the contents and reliability of the linked websites and does not necessarily endorse the views expressed in them. Mere presence of the link or its listing on this website should not be assumed as endorsement of any kind. We cannot guarantee that these links will work all the time and we have no control over availability of linked pages.

Links to Ministry of Drinking Water and Sanitation Website by other websites/portals  
Prior permission is required before hyperlinks are directed from any website/portal to this site. Permission for the same, stating the nature of the content on the pages from where the link has to be given and the exact language of the Hyperlink should be obtained by sending a request to stake holder.

* * *

## Terms of use

Disclaimer  
This Portal is designed, developed and hosted by National Informatics Centre under the aegis of Ministry of Drinking Water and Sanitation (MDWS).The contents for this website are provided by MDWS/State Governments.  
Though all efforts have been made to ensure the accuracy and currency of the content of this Portal, the same should not be construed as a statement of law or used for any legal purposes. MDWS does not accept any responsibility in relation to the accuracy, completeness, usefulness or otherwise, of the contents. Users are advised to verify/check any information with the relevant Government department(s) and/or other source(s), and to obtain any appropriate professional advice before acting on the information provided in the website. In no event will the government or MDWS be liable for any expense, loss or damage including, without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any expense, loss or damage whatsoever arising from use, or loss of use, of data, arising out of or in connection with the use of this website.  
Links to other websites that have been included on this website are provided for public convenience only. MDWS is not responsible for the contents or reliability of linked websites and does not necessarily endorse the view expressed within them or guarantee the availability of such linked pages at all times.  
Material featured on this Portal may be reproduced free of charge after taking proper permission by sending a mail to us. However, the material has to be reproduced accurately and not to be used in a derogatory manner or in a misleading context. Wherever the material is being published or issued to others, the source must be prominently acknowledged. However, the permission to reproduce this material shall not extend to any material which is identified as being copyright of a third party. Authorization to reproduce such material must be obtained from the departments/copyright holders concerned.  
These terms and conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the Indian Laws. Any dispute arising under these terms and conditions shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of India.

* * *

## Privacy Policy

MDWS website does not automatically capture any specific personal information from you, (like name, phone number or e-mail address), that allows us to identify you individually.  
If this website requests you to provide personal information, you will be informed for the particular purposes for which the information is gathered and adequate security measures will be taken to protect your personal information.  
MDWS does not sell or share any personally identifiable information volunteered on this website to any third party (public/private). Any information provided to this Portal will be protected from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

* * *

## Copyright Policy

All the contents available on the Ministry of Drinking Water and Sanitation website are indigenously developed by Ministry of Drinking Water and Sanitation and there is no third party content present on this website. If any third party content is present on the website then Ministry of Drinking Water and Sanitation has obtained the due permissions as per the copyright policies of the third parties whose contents are published on this website.

Contents of this website may not be reproduced partially or fully, without due permission from the Ministry of Drinking Water and Sanitation. It’s content, if referred to and/or forms a part of content of another website, the content-source must be appropriately acknowledged. The contents of this website cannot be used in any misleading or objectionable context.
